Contact

cchawla@ec.iitr.ac.in

www.linkedin.com/in/chinmayachawla (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Leadership
Business Strategy
Management Consulting

Certifications

Introduction to Data Analytics for Business

Predictive Modeling and Analytics

Honors-Awards

Gold Medal | Ashoka Tech For Change | 8th Inter IIT Technical Meet Winner | Quantathon 2020 AIR 6 | All India Abacus Competition | UCMAS

Chinmaya Chawla

Summer Intern at PwC India | Sophomore at IIT Roorkee Haridwar

Summary

Experienced professional with a past of having worked in management. Skilled in identifying, structuring and solving problems with added asset of software background. Immense experience of Public Speaking along with Leadership and Networking skills. Holds great knowledge of finance and has undertaken consulting projects.

Firm and able professional pursuing a Bachelor's Degree in Electronics and Communication Engineering from the Indian Institute of Technology, Roorkee.

Experience

ShARE IIT Roorkee

1 year 11 months

Manager , Campus Activities February 2020 - Present (7 months)

Senior Member October 2019 - February 2020 (5 months)

Junior Member October 2018 - September 2019 (1 year)

Indian Institute of Technology, Roorkee

Manager | Industry Connect | Student Technical Council
January 2020 - Present (8 months)

Networked with industry leaders and helped sign various partnerships for the Institute Technical Council.

PwC India Consultant May 2020 - August 2020 (4 months) Gurgaon, Haryana Personal Guru (Tecuto Education Solutions Pvt. Ltd.)
Personal Development Mentor
April 2020 - May 2020 (2 months)

I mentored and guided a pool of 10 students from economically backward areas to overcome the difficulties faced throughout the journey of preparation for entrance exams.

Inter IIT Cultural Meet
Manager
December 2018 - December 2018 (1 month)
IIT Roorkee

Managed an event that saw participation from over 2000 participants coming from 23 IITs across India.

Education

Indian Institute of Technology, Roorkee
Bachelor's degree, Electronics and Communication
Engineering · (2018 - 2022)

Lav Kush Sr. Sec. School (2016 - 2018)

Nosegay Public School - India (2007 - 2016)